Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection ca. 1982-1994 MSS 120 MSS.120
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: French Manuscripts
  - Collignon, Yves. 'Pour memoire', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 205)
  - Colomb, Laurent. 'Zang num num', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 206)
  - Confort Claude. 'Le passage', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 207)
  - Corbier, Annie. 'L.', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 208)
  - Cordrie, Lorette. 'A force de planter des clous dans le ciel', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 209)
  - Cordrie, Lorette. 'Ressac', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 210)
  - Cosson, Nathalie. 'La fortresse de l'ange', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 211)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'Boomerang!', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 212)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'Brummell aen', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 213)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'Nous, Charles XII', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 214)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'Tout va de mieux en mieux', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 215)
  - Costaz, Gilles. 'Le calepin', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 216)
  - Coupet, Philippe. 'Sommnus', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 217)
  - Coureau, Pascal. 'Sanctions et gratifications', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 218)
  - Cousse, Raymond. 'Strate pour deux jambons', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 219)
  - Coutarnoux, Frans. 'Ma vedette americaine', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 220)
  - Dabo, Gabriel. 'L'attente', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 221)
  - Daigle, Jean. 'Colette et Sido (une conversation)', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 222)
  - Daigle, Jean. 'Verlaine-Rimbaud/Rimbaud-Verlaine', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 223)
  - Dalbray, Muse. 'Avant la pilule', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 224)
  - Dalbray, Muse. 'Fra Sylvere', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 225)
  - Dalbray, Muse. 'La joyeuse aventure de Jehan de Paris', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 226)
  - Dalbray, Muse. 'La malediction des templiers', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 227)
  - Dalbray, Muse. 'On prend les autres et on recommence', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 228)
  - Dalbray, Muse. 'Le r pass1789)', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 229)
  - Dal Farra, Catherine. 'Annoncez-vous!', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 230)
  - Dambury, Gerty. 'Camille et Justine', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 231)
  - Dambury, Gerty. 'Caremes', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 232)
  - Dambury, Gerty. 'Madjaka', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 233)
  - Dambury, Gerty. 'Rabordaille', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 234)
  - Danailov, Gueorgui and Obbov, Ivan. 'Le cas Adonis', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 235)
  - Danaud, Jean-Claude. 'Un ouvrage de dames', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 236)
  - Daoudi, Ivane. 'My Sweet DestinyObcession', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 237)
  - Daoudi, Ivane. 'Rage', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 238)
  - Daoudi, Ivane. 'Teltow kanal', undated; 31142040610258 (Box I.6, Folder 239)
  - Darnal, Jean-Claude. 'Le petit theater', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 240)
  - Daugreilh, Xavier. 'Accalmies passags', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 241)
  - Daumas, Jean-Paul. 'Le cimeti des elephants', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 242)
  - Debas, Philippe. 'Jeanne d'Arc', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 243)
  - Debord, Claude-Lold. 'Anatole Durand', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 244)
  - Delaruelle, Marc. 'Dissection d'un amour pour personages sans nom', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 246)
  - Delbo, Charlotte. 'La capitulation', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 247)
  - Delbo, Charlotte. 'La capitulation', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 248)
  - Delbo, Charlotte. 'Et toi, comment as-tu fait?', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 249)
  - Delbo, Charlotte. 'Et toi, comment as-tu fait?', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 250)
  - Delbo, Charlotte. 'Les homes', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 251)
  - Delome, Didier. 'Le voyage en Italie (incomplete)', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 252)
  - Delome, Didier. 'Le voyage en Italie', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 253)
  - Delore, Elizabeth. 'Inukuo', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 254)
  - Demaille, Patrick. 'Coup de cendre', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 255)
  - Demer, Jean. 'Sur la plage', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 256)
  - Demptos, Andr'Anahita', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 257)
  - Demptos, Andr'La danseuse au pied bot', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 258)
  - Demptos, Andr'Le mirage de Gilda', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 259)
  - Denis, S. 'La prodigieuse.', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 260)
  - Desgagn Yves. 'Je ne t'aime pas', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 261)
  - Deslias, Philippe. 'Geronimo', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 262)
  - Diaby, Irahima. 'Blues sur Seine ou en pensant osephine Baker', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 263)
  - Diawara, Alain. 'Traversant Johannesburg', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 264)
  - Dib, Mohammed. 'La fiancdu printemps', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 265)
  - Didier-Weill, Alain. 'Le banc', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 266)
  - Didier-Weill, Alain. 'Basse surveillance', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 267)
  - Didier-Weill, Alain. 'Trois cases blanches', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 268)
  - Didier-Weill, Alain. 'Vienne 1913', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 269)
  - Didi-Huberman, Georges. 'Le fugueur phonetique et la mere amerique', undated; 31142040610266 (Box I.7, Folder 270)
  - Djanaf, Fabienne. 'La vache enrag, undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 271)
  - Djedidi, Hafedh. 'La danse des passions', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 272)
  - Djedidi, Hafedh. 'L'envers et l'endroit ou un repas pas commes autres', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 273)
  - Djedidi, Hafedh. 'Forum des femmes', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 274)
  - Doazan, Jacques. 'Un chambre sans fene', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 275)
  - Dobreva, Jana. 'Le silence des myrtilles', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 276)
  - Doleron, George. 'Vous avez dit oui, ou bien vous avez dit non?', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 277)
  - DorIsabelle. 'Cr et Drana', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 278)
  - Douby, Bernard. 'Un anglais au fond de la baleine', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 279)
  - Douby, Bernard. 'Un homme nu dans les myosotis', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 280)
  - Doutreligne, Louise. 'Quand speedoux s'endort', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 281)
  - Doutreligne, Louise. 'Femme a la porte cochere', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 282)
  - Doutreligne, Louise. 'Qui est Lucie syn'?', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 283)
  - Drai, Martine. 'Meurtre', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 284)
  - Drai, Martine. 'Messe', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 285)
  - Drai, Martine. 'Il suffit de peu', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 286)
  - Drai, Martine. 'Presentation d'un crime', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 287)
  - Drai, Martine. 'Lezardes', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 288)
  - Drai, Martine. 'L'heure', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 289)
  - Driss, Ilias. 'Retour, retours', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 290)
  - Dubois, Renaniel. 'Being at Home with Claude', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 291)
  - Dubois, Renaniel. 'Le printemps, Monsieur Deslauriers', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 292)
  - Dulac, Paul-Gabriel. 'Si c'est un beau jour pour rsir', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 293)
  - Dupont, Emeric. 'L'incomparable destin de Mara Rosenstern', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 294)
  - Dupois, Gilbert. 'Mon oncle Marcel', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 295)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'Vera Baxter', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 296)
  - Durringer, Xavier. 'La quille', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 297)
  - Dussant, Andr'Un depart en retraite', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 298)
  - D'Usseau, Emmanuel. 'Les vacances de L', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 299)
  - Dutaillis, Olivier. 'On s'entendait si bien', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 300)
  - Ebner, Jacques. 'Corps oeurs', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 301)
  - Efoui, Kossi. Le crise de culture et autres rexions (interview with Bernard Chenuaud)', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 302)
  - Efoui, Kossi Yoshua. 'Le petit fr du rameur', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 303)
  - Efoui, Josuossi. La veritt la mort de Pitagaba cont sure le trottoir de la radio', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 304)
  - Ehret, Odile. 'Roissy', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 305)
  - ion, Robert. 'Vous avez dit Bizet?', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 306)
  - Emond, Paul. 'Est-ce que vous revez?', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 307)
  - Ernotte, Andr'L'humble courage des iles', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 308)
  - Er Saoz, Roro. 'President Roro', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 309)
  - Etcherelli, Claire. 'Germinal, an III', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 310)
  - Evain, Aurore. 'Femmes d'attente', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 311)
  - Fabien, Mich. 'Dnire', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 312)
  - Fadel, Youssef. 'Bouhafna', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 313)
  - Fadel, Youssef. 'Les topographes', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 314)
  - Fall, Marouba. 'Adja, la militante', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 315)
  - Fall, Marouba. 'L'eau et le feu', undated; 31142040610274 (Box I.8, Folder 316)
  - Farcy, Bernard and Guerineau, Clotilde. 'Comme un oiseau qui frappe au carreau', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 317)
  - Fares, Oscar. 'Un vieil amour tout neuf', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 318)
  - Fargeau, Jean-Pol. 'Beaucoup love', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 319)
  - Fargeau, Jean-Pol. 'Brrivi, br/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 320)
  - Farhoud, Abla. 'Apatride', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 321)
  - Farhoud, Abla. 'La camisole rouge', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 322)
  - Farhoud, Abla. 'Jeux de patience', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 323)
  - Farhoud, Abla. 'Quand j'is grande', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 324)
  - Fathy, Safaa. 'Terreur', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 325)
  - Faucher, Martin. 'La fille de Christophe Colomb', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 326)
  - Faure, Philippe. 'Le poumon imaginaire ou Moli dans un souffl/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 327)
  - Fenwick, Jean-No 'Calamity Jane', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 328)
  - Ferrane, Jean-Frans. '(Untitled)', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 329)
  - Ferrane, Jean-Frans. 'Toile de fond', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 330)
  - Feugas, Franse. 'Interieur, jour', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 331)
  - Figuiere, Sandrine. 'Deux ames au fond d'un verre', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 332)
  - Florensa, Jean Manel. 'Au dernier ge du Chihuahua H', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 333)
  - Florensa, Jean Manel. 'L'extraordinaire cas de Michael K.', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 334)
  - Florensa, Jean Manel. 'Le rendez-vous de la maison jaune', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 335)
  - Floris, Alexandre. 'Heros', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 336)
  - Forgeau, Filip. 'Le dealer ou correspondences du desespoir', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 337)
  - Forgeau, Filip. 'Jimmy et Boris dans la neige ou les egares', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 338)
  - Forgeau, Filip. 'Les quatre saisons, debut et fin', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 339)
  - Forn, Tony. 'Destin', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 340)
  - Fourcade, Gaulthier. 'L'amicale des contrevenants', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 341)
  - Fourchard, Beno 'Les illusions d'optique', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 342)
  - Fourchard, Beno 'Juillet au paradis', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 343)
  - Frank, ienne. 'Kaselezo', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 344)
  - Fripiat, Bernard. 'Churchill/Hess la decision!', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 345)
  - Fritsch, Luc. 'Ruines', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 346)
  - Futterer, Igor. 'La cigone n'a qu'une t!', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 347)
  - Gallaire, Fatima. 'Les circoncis', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 348)
  - Gallaire, Fatima. 'Les derniers seigneurs', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 349)
  - Gallaire, Fatima. 'Position de travail', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 350)
  - Gallaire, Fatima. 'La sublime elephante', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 351)
  - Gallaire, Fatima. 'Temoignage contre un homme sterile', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 352)
  - Gallaire-Bourega, Fatima. Haou Jitiou Vous s venusla ou il y a quelques tombes!', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 353)
  - Galmier, Daniel. 'Saint-Justin des fosses', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 354)
  - Galy, Jean-Paul. 'Zirelia', undated; 31142040610282 (Box I.9, Folder 355)
  - Gampez, Sapi. 'Le vent et la pluie', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 356)
  - Gander, Eric. 'Fernando, par accident?', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 357)
  - Ganzl, Serge. 'La desherence', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 358)
  - Gazarian, Pierre. 'L'inventaire', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 359)
  - Gazarian, Pierre. 'Les orphelins sauvages', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 360)
  - Gazarian, Pierre. 'Parlez-moi doucement, je suis sourd', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 361)
  - Gnas, Gratien. 'Bousille et les justes', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 362)
  - Genet, Jean. 'Splendid's', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 363)
  - Genvrin, Emmanuel. 'Baudelaire au paradis', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 364)
  - Genvrin, Emmanuel. 'L'esclavage des negres', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 365)
  - Genvrin, Emmanuel. 'Etuves', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 367)
  - George-Marie, Nicolas. 'Zone rouge pour homme egare', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 368)
  - Georges, Marc Michel. 'Amuseries et tragelismes', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 369)
  - Georges, Marc Michel. 'Le tignous', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 370)
  - Gershman, Judith. 'Blackout', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 371)
  - Gershman, Judith. 'Les letters de la vie', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 372)
  - Gershman, Judith. 'Soleil noir', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 373)
  - Gershman, Judith. 'Soleil nuit', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 374)
  - Gershman, Judith. 'La vallde l'ombre de la mort', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 375)
  - Gerstein, Serge. 'Eddy', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 376)
  - Gibaud, Alain. 'En ce bas monde', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 377)
  - Gibaud, Alain. 'Jean de Tailleroc', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 378)
  - Gibaud, Alain. 'La maison est close', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 379)
  - Gille, Andrnd Charras, Charles. 'Le president', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 380)
  - Ginoyer, Alexandre. 'La prix de pouvoir', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 381)
  - Giraud, Marc. 'En esperance', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 382)
  - Giraud, Marc. 'Savalete de lange', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 383)
  - Giraudoux, Jean. 'L'Apollon de Bellac', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 384)
  - Glass, Pascale Blanchard. 'Le geographe', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 385)
  - Glass, Pascale Blanchard. 'Mes voisines d'en haut', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 386)
  - Gleizes, Pascal. 'Le fil du rasoir', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 387)
  - Goma, Vale. 'En attendant l'', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 388)
  - Gorasny, Patrik. 'Le chariot des graces', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 389)
  - Gorasny, Patrik. 'Le nebuleuse d'orion', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 390)
  - Gorasny, Patrik. 'La ronde de nuit ou l'aube du 15 juillet', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 391)
  - Gosse, Olivier. 'Cargo', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 392)
  - Gosse, Olivier. 'Naro', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 393)
  - Gracci, Gracco. 'La pi', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 394)
  - Granger, Bernard. 'H des abattoirs', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 395)
  - Granger, Bernard. 'Le tropique du mammouth', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 396)
  - Granouillet, Gilles. 'Chroniques des oublidu tour', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 397)
  - Granouillet, Gilles. 'Vodou', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 398)
  - Grego, Moni. 'La traversou un aller simple', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 399)
  - Grinberg, M. et M. 'Le caract de Madame de Bruy', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 400)
  - Grumberg, Jean-Claude. 'Maman revient pauvre orphelin', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 401)
  - Guerdon, David. 'Le dormeur dans l'alcove', undated; 31142040610290 (Box I.10, Folder 402)
  - Guerot, Jean Pierre. 'Un lien de soie', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 403)
  - Guers, Marie Josephe. 'Redites-moi des choses tenders', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 404)
  - Guers, Marie Josephe. 'Le temps d'un trajet', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 405)
  - Guilbert, Pierre. 'Les sur les choses usuelles', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 406)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'L'atelier du peintre', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 407)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'L'atelier du peintre', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 408)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'L'atelier du peintre (final version)', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 409)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'L'auberge verte', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 410)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'La maison des hommes', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 411)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'La maison transparente', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 412)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'La passerelle', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 413)
  - Guingane, Jean-Pierre. 'Le cri de l'espoir', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 414)
  - Guitry, Sascha. 'Nono', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 415)
  - Gustin, Pascale. 'Les tricheurs', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 416)
  - Gyr, Brigitte. 'Chocolat', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 417)
  - Gyr, Brigitte. 'Deux=trois', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 418)
  - Hafkin, Jo 'Alexandra David-N and snow', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 419)
  - Haghighat, Chapour. 'Un songe d'hiver', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 420)
  - Ha Victor. 'La frappe', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 421)
  - Hakim, Adel. 'Corps', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 422)
  - Hamelin, Lancelot. 'La plaie', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 423)
  - Hanai, Brahim. 'C'est arrive abel', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 424)
  - Hanai, Brahim. 'La nuit ou Scherezade se tut', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 425)
  - Harrisson, Sstien. 'Floes', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 426)
  - Hud, Hugues. 'L'instant parfait', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 427)
  - Herbette, Jean-Claude. 'Les penitents', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 428)
  - HeurtYves. 'Un requiem sous les iles', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 429)
  - Hipeau, Valerie. 'Le silence des arbres', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 430)
  - Hislen, Jean-No 'L'homme aux pieds', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 431)
  - Hourantier, Marie-Jos'Ma sogona ma laide', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 432)
  - Hourez, Roland. 'Proth', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 433)
  - Huet, Laurence. 'Ezel ezem ezen', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 434)
  - Huet, Laurence. 'Ezel ezem ezen', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 435)
  - Huet, Laurence. 'Pis sans conviction', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 436)
  - Huet, Laurence. 'My Sweet Embraceable You', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 437)
  - Hugodot, Philippe. 'Pedro II ou la flamme et la cendre', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 438)
  - Hugues-Heraud, Denis. 'Servanne', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 439)
  - Huster, Francis. 'Putzi', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 440)
  - Inesta, Pierre-Luc. 'Soleil levant', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 441)
  - Inkimo, Henri. 'La chambre bleue', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 442)
  - Inkimo, Henri. 'Leon', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 443)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'La cantatrice chauve', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 444)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'Les chaises', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 445)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'Jacques ou la soumission', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 446)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'Jacques ou la soumission', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 447)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'La le', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 448)
  - Irlande, Christine. 'Rouge it le rire des femmes', undated; 31142040610308 (Box I.11, Folder 449)
  - IsraLe Pelletier, Marc. 'Le globe', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 450)
  - Jacque, Thadee. 'Embrassez la petite Juliette', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 451)
  - JaffIsabelle. 'Hier je suis morte', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 452)
  - JaffIsabelle. 'Le mocassin et l'escarpin', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 453)
  - Jaibi, Fadhel. 'Familia', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 454)
  - Jaomanoro, David. 'Le dernier caiman', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 455)
  - Jaomanoro, David. 'Le dernier caiman', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 456)
  - Jaffeux, Marc. 'Mourir dans une salle de bain', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 457)
  - Jean, Andr'A propos de la demoiselle qui pleurait', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 458)
  - Jeanjean, Dominique. 'La fille prodigue', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 459)
  - Jeanvoine, Mich. 'La vigie', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 460)
  - Jemaer, Sstien. 'Joker', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 461)
  - Jouanneau, Jo 'Le bourrichon', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 462)
  - Joubert, Suzanne. 'Les chants de l'ordinaire', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 463)
  - Jourdheuil, Michel. 'Id-fleurs', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 464)
  - Kacimi, Mohamed. 'La confession d'Abraham', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 465)
  - Kaplan, Leslie. 'L'exl'usine', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 466)
  - Kalouaz, Ahmed. 'Le vol du papillon', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 467)
  - Kalouaz, Ahmed. 'Territoire', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 468)
  - Kalouaz, Ahmed. 'Avant quimper', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 469)